<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
    <Bingo.Letter.ObjectiveComplete.label>Bingo Objective Completed!</Bingo.Letter.ObjectiveComplete.label>
    <Bingo.Letter.ObjectiveComplete.text>You have completed the objective '{0}'.</Bingo.Letter.ObjectiveComplete.text>
    <Bingo.Letter.BingoComplete.label>BINGO!</Bingo.Letter.BingoComplete.label>
    <Bingo.Letter.BingoComplete.text>You have completed a line of bingo! You currently have {0} bingo(s).\nYou achieved this milestone in {1} in-game time, and {2} in real time.</Bingo.Letter.BingoComplete.text>
    <Bingo.Letter.BingoBoardComplete.label>All Objectives Completed!</Bingo.Letter.BingoBoardComplete.label>
    <Bingo.Letter.BingoBoardComplete.text>You have completed all of the available objectives! Congratulations!\nYou completed the board in {1} in-game time, and {2} in real time.</Bingo.Letter.BingoBoardComplete.text>
    <Bingo.Letter.MilestoneRecord>Line {0}: {1} IGT, {2} RTA</Bingo.Letter.MilestoneRecord>
    <Bingo.Letter.StrangeSign1>In an instant, a strange psychic wave passed through your colonists. You don't know where it came from, but rest assured that the wave is harmless - your colonists will be a bit happier for a few days.</Bingo.Letter.StrangeSign1>
    <!-- Choices -->
    <Bingo.Letter.RewardsPower>I seek power</Bingo.Letter.RewardsPower>
    <Bingo.Letter.RewardsLife>I seek life</Bingo.Letter.RewardsLife>
    <Bingo.Letter.RewardsDeath>I seek death</Bingo.Letter.RewardsDeath>
    <Bingo.Letter.RewardsStrength>I seek strength</Bingo.Letter.RewardsStrength>
    <Bingo.Letter.RewardsPawn>I seek you</Bingo.Letter.RewardsPawn>
    <Bingo.Letter.RewardsNothing>I seek none</Bingo.Letter.RewardsNothing>
    <!-- Letters from Archotech mind -->
    <Bingo.Letter.ArchotechReward.label>Archotech call</Bingo.Letter.ArchotechReward.label>
    <Bingo.Letter.ArchotechReward1.text>You received a message coming from a distant archotech mind. Your actions on the bingo board has attracted attentions of a powerful being. You aren't sure of their purposes, but they assured you that they only have good intentions.\n\nTo prove that to you, they're willing to grant you a special reward. You just need to reply to their question:\n\n"What do you seek?"</Bingo.Letter.ArchotechReward1.text>
    <Bingo.Letter.ArchotechReward2.text>The archotech mind came back to you. They seem sastified with your progresss so far. They're willing to grant you another gift.\n\nAgain, they asked you:\n\n"What do you seek?"</Bingo.Letter.ArchotechReward2.text>
    <Bingo.Letter.ArchotechReward3.text>The archotech mind came back to you. They're here to deliver to you one more reward. They also told you one thing: complete everything the board has, and they shall give you the ultimate rewards they're willing to offer.\n\nOnce again, they asked you:\n\n"What do you seek?"</Bingo.Letter.ArchotechReward3.text>
    <Bingo.Letter.ArchotechRewardArrived.label>Rewards arrived</Bingo.Letter.ArchotechRewardArrived.label>
    <Bingo.Letter.ArchotechRewardArrived.text>Falling from the sky, the rewards you seek has arrived. The archotech mind shuts their communication with you.\nComplete more bingo lines to potentially attract their attentions again.</Bingo.Letter.ArchotechRewardArrived.text>
    <!-- Final Call/Ending -->
    <Bingo.Letter.StrangeSign2>What will the archotech mind tell you now?</Bingo.Letter.StrangeSign2>
    <Bingo.Letter.ArchotechRewardLastCall.label>Archotech final call</Bingo.Letter.ArchotechRewardLastCall.label>
    <Bingo.Letter.ArchotechRewardLastCall.text>The archotech mind contacted you.\nThey congratulated you for completing every challenges there are on the bingo board. Not many colonies have been as dedicated as yours to complete a total blackout.\n\nAs promised, they shall give you their ultimate rewards: an assortments of rare archotechnologies and powerful treasures, all of which might take a colony many decades to accumulate all of. They will also ensure your safety on this rimworld - any arriving lethal threat to this planet will immediately vanish - including any arriving planetkiller weapons.\nIn addition, they will also give you an option to prestige - to receive a new bingo board. Complete the bingo board again to once more receive more rewards from them. They will assign an AI persona to handle the task of monitoring your progress as well as delivering rewards.\n\nYou just need to say yes. So, for one last time, they asked you:\n\n"What do you seek?"</Bingo.Letter.ArchotechRewardLastCall.text>
    <Bingo.Letter.FinalRewardsTreasure>I seek treasure</Bingo.Letter.FinalRewardsTreasure>
    <Bingo.Credits>The archotech mind shuts its communication with you, for perhaps the last time.\n\nYou're now in possession of some of the rarest technologies available on this rimworld, all of which might take generations for others to obtain.\n\nBut what if you can get even more?\n\nShortly afterwards, an AI persona came in contact with you. It belongs to the archotech mind, and it is ready to give you even more rewards, should you choose to partake in this bingo challenge once again.\n\nWhat is your choice?\n\nYour statistics:</Bingo.Credits>
    <Bingo.CreditsSelfInsert>Thanks for playing my Bingo mod! - LongCT_</Bingo.CreditsSelfInsert>
    <Bingo.Letter.ArchotechFinalRewardRewardArrived.text>Your rewards have arrived.\nYou can continue with a new bingo board by selecting 'Prestige' on your Bingo tab.</Bingo.Letter.ArchotechFinalRewardRewardArrived.text>
    <Bingo.PlanetkillerStopped.label>Planetkillers disintegrated</Bingo.PlanetkillerStopped.label>
    <Bingo.PlanetkillerStopped.text>Records shown that all incoming planetkillers have vanished into thin air. You're unsure how, or where they went, but they now no longer pose a threat to this planet.</Bingo.PlanetkillerStopped.text>
    <!-- Prestige -->
    <Bingo.Letter.ArchotechRewardPrestige.label>AI persona's call</Bingo.Letter.ArchotechRewardPrestige.label>
    <Bingo.Letter.ArchotechRewardPrestige.text>The bingo archotech mind's AI persona has noticed your progress on the new bingo board. It will now let you choose a reward.\n"What do you seek?"</Bingo.Letter.ArchotechRewardPrestige.text>
    <Bingo.Letter.ArchotechFinalRewardPrestige.label>AI persona's congratulatory message</Bingo.Letter.ArchotechFinalRewardPrestige.label>
    <Bingo.Letter.ArchotechFinalRewardPrestige.text>The bingo archotech mind's AI persona congratulate you on your bingo board completion. This is your {0} completions in total. It will now give you the grand rewards.</Bingo.Letter.ArchotechFinalRewardPrestige.text>
    <Bingo.Letter.ArchotechRewardArrivedPrestige.text>Falling from the sky, the rewards you seek has arrived. The AI persona shuts its communication with you.\nComplete more bingo lines to potentially attract its attentions again.</Bingo.Letter.ArchotechRewardArrivedPrestige.text>
</LanguageData>